That's hard.
Yeah.
That's dirty hard.
Oh, man!
Remember who
we're fighting for, gentleman.
Bring it on,
bring it on! Bring it on!
I like this house.
I think we're gonna take it.
Yes, sir. See you in a bit.
Let us know
if there's any changes.
Moving.
Sir, there's a wall up here.
Copy that.
Why is there a wall?
It's, er, two apartments.
Top and bottom floor.
Two houses.
Understood.
Break it.
Let's go. Come on.
Redman 0-6, Profane 5-4.
Er, contact individual headed
north to your location.
Civilian traffic east to west
of your structure.
Er, prox, Profane 5-4-10-8.
Er, Profane 5-5-10-5.
All stations this net,
all stations this net.
Clearance operations
are complete.
All friendly units
are RTB at this time.
Be advised you have
new friendly location.
Baker Company has moved
north-west of your location.
Two klicks.
Understand. Copy all.
Sir. Baker Company were here.
They're now here.
Two kilometers
in this position.
Copy that.
Manchu,
stand by for sit rep.
Say when ready to copy. Over.
Frogman
, send your traffic.
At 0-niner-7,
we observed people probing
our position from the east.
Section Papa 1-0,
building 1-7-4,
east of route Boiler.
At 0-9-1-2,
we saw massing
at building 1-7-5
north of route Spartan. Break.
At 0-niner-1-6,
a blue Daewoo with MAMs
north on route Lakers.
How copy. Over.
Yeah, Frogman, repeat
everything after blue Daewoo.
Over.
Manchu, a blue Daewoo
with military-age males
traveling north
on route Lakers.
Over.
Copy all.
Do you have any more traffic
for my station? Over.
Negative, Manchu.
How's your signal?
It's good now.
Still intermittent.
Cool.
Got eyes on the north-west
corner of building four.
Is that white Hilux
still there?
No, the Hilux pulled out,
like...
five minutes ago.
But I got a male...
white shirt,
dark tracksuit pants
looking at our position.
That sound familiar?
Negative. ID any weapons?
No weapons.
He's gone.
Is he going on the list?
Single MAM, white shirt,
dark tracksuit pants,
building four,
north-west corner.
By the way, my, uh...
my blue Nike hoodie
went missing off the base.
If you see somebody out there
wearing it, let me know.
Don't shoot 'em,
either. I want it back.
Yeah, I'll try.
We should check that run of
buildings to the West again.
I mean, you could step right
across those rooftops
-if you wanted.
-Yeah.
-Walk right to us, right?
-Mmm-hmm.
How's it going, Dozer?
Baker 6 tracking.
Baker 6 out.
Huh?
How's it going?
Going well.
Okay.
-That's that new guy energy.
-Mmm-hmm.
How is it down there?
Cigarettes and tea.
You want tea?
No, I'll pass.
What you got up here?
- Peekers.
- Where?
Corners
of building four.
Oh, I gotcha.
I can't see anything.
Oh, he's back.
-White T-shirt?
-Mmm-hmm.
Alpha Two, this is One.
We might have guys starting
to move on our position.
Maybe because they heard you
sledging through
that fucking wall all night.
We could hear every strike.
Why didn't you use a charge?
I didn't wanna make a noise.
Not sure
that worked out for you.
Profane 5-4,
this is Redman 6.
Can you slew your sensor
to the east of my position
on one-zero-zero meters
on building per GRG?
Call contact.
Redman 0-6, stand by.
Turning.
Prox 5-5, track OP-1.
Profane 5-5 looking.
Contact, corner, IC personnel.
Hey, er, we got an individual
who was peeking
on the north-west corner
of building 4.
He's disappeared to the west.
Do you see anybody hanging
around that corner? Over.
Stand by. Looking.
5-4 contacts.
Just be advised he's been
probing our position.
Do you see any massing
or suspicious activity
that can indicate a threat?
Over.
Negative, 0-6.
Er, you're all good.
Roger that, Profane.
Redman out.
You keep an eye
on that for me.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Headscarf,
red-green jacket.
Peeking again.
That's the fourth fucking time
he's done that.
Is he peeking or probing?
Peeking with serious intent
to probe.
How many times are we gonna
let this guy do this?
I'm gonna relay to OP-2.
Hey, Cowboy,
give me a heads-up
if you see this guy
come to your position.
Headscarf, red-green jacket.
Copy.
We're getting a build-up
of activity here, too.
I had a pair of guys in
blue jeans probing, twice.
I have two MAMs of that
description,
just showed up here.
Blue jeans, one red shirt.
Yeah, that's them.
Well, it looks like they're
getting their Jihad on.
Alpha One,
Bravo One, we're in a TIC.
We're getting rockets
and small arms fire.
We're all good right now,
but we're pulling air
to our position.
Roger that.
Check in with BDA when able.
Wilco.
Alpha Five,
this is Bravo Four.
Hey, I think we're gonna need
to pull Profane
to our AO. Over.
Roger that, Bravo Four.
Redman 0-6, this is Profane.
We have been re-tasked.
We're checking off station
at this time.
Roger that, Profane.
Hey, is there a reason
they're pulling air from us
and not sourcing it
from somewhere else?
-I'm on it.
-What's up?
We just lost air support.
Pushing to Bravo.
Wild Eagle Base,
Wild Eagle 2-4.
Profane 5-4 checked
off station at this time.
I'm looking for any available
air assets. Over.
That's not good.
2-4.
Roger, stand by.
They're troops in contact.
Aff-irm, Wild Eagle Base.
Standing by.
Hey, Cowboy,
we're getting movement here.
Yeah,
the streets are
definitely clearing out.
Yeah, I'm tracking.
Captain Erik.
It's not good.
They say they call on
all Muslims for Jihad.
Jihad to come now.
To kill you.
To kill Americans.
Yeah, that sucks.
Yeah, that does suck.
All right. Go keep lower deck
locked down.
You understand?
Hey. Downstairs.
Keep it fucking secure.
Okay.
Do you think
they're gonna do it?
I think we're about
to find out.
You've been in there
for a while.
Yeah, I live in there now.
All right, swap out.
I'll relieve you.
Yes, sir.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Hey, Frank.
Jump on this a second.
I'm out of dip
and I gotta stretch, dude.
Yeah, I got you.
I got a blue Opel
moving east to west
towards OP-1 position. Over.
Roger that, blue Opel.
Blue Opel is approaching
building three.
Three MAMs
just exited vehicle.
Correction, make that four.
Heading into building three.
PKM!
Fuck.
Cowboy, the fourth MAM
had a PKM.
I couldn't get the shot off.
Over.
Weak.
What happened?
I, er...
I couldn't get him.
He, um...
He ran inside too fast.
Weak.
Yeah,
we have definite massing.
Hey, six MAMs just exited
building five in my sector.
I'm seeing the same
where we are.
Yeah, building three.
I'm gonna take a piss.
Oh, fuck.
Grenade!
Our position
is under small arms fire.
Frank, Tommy, Elliott?
You good?
Motherfucker.
Move!
Movement, balcony!
- Elliott?
- I'm out.
Stand up. You hurt?
- Look at me.
- No, I'm good,
I'm good. Check on Elliott.
Think our gear's
still in there.
Down.
Lift your arm up. Look at me.
How bad is it?
Yeah, we're gonna need
a cas-evac.
- All right.
- Okay.
This is Frogman-6 Romeo.
We are troops in contact
at our last known position.
More info to follow. Stand by.
Wild Eagle Base,
Wild Eagle 2-4.
We are troops in contact.
Requesting immediate
air support. Over.
Alpha Two, this is One.
We've had grenades
thrown into our position.
Copy, One.
We're in contact too.
Elliott is injured.
Are we coming to you
-or are you coming to us?
-Fuck.
- Stand by.
Hey!
Downstairs.
Keep it fucking secure.
Alpha
One, we're moving to you.
We'll let you know
when we're inbound.
Yeah. All right.
All OPs are under attack.
This is what we're gonna do.
We're gonna collapse to the
first deck, cas-evac Elliott.
Break it down.
Let's get ready to move.
-Yes, sir.
-Collapse. Collapse.
Yes, sir.
OP-2, what's your status?
-I gotta get the receiver.
-Sir, sir, sir, sir!
-What are you doing?
-I gotta get the receiver.
We're in a TIC,
on our way.
Mac, not a good idea.
This is
Frogman-6 Romeo.
We need a cas-evac at
our last known position. Over.
-Cover me.
-Yeah.
Frogman, confirm
sector and building number.
OP-1 location as follows:
Papa 1-0, building 5-8.
How copy? Over.
Frogman,
read back as follows:
Papa 1-0, building 5-8.
Good read-back.
Frogman,
any amplifying remarks? Over.
Negative.
No amplifying remarks.
Just need a cas-evac.
Advise on ETA. Over.
Copy that.
Stand by. Over.
Um, guys,
my shit is still in there.
-Where is it?
-I don't fucking know, dude.
It's in there somewhere.
And my shit's in there too.
All right, I... I got it.
Alpha One,
we're moving to you.
We'll let you know
when we're inbound.
- Copy.
- Shit.
Tommy, you see where
that gunfire came from?
Um, I saw a guy.
They shot through the window.
I can't find it.
- It's in there, bro.
- I can't fucking find it, man.
Frogman-6 Romeo,
cas-evac is inbound.
Callsign Bushmaster
on ID 7-5-5.
ETA 1-0 mikes. Over.2
Copy. Bushmaster 7-5-5. Over.
Bradley launched.
ETA 10 minutes.
Ten minutes!
All right. Stack up.
Get ready to collapse.
We're moving down.
Yes, sir. Sir.
I still think there's dudes
on our roof.
Yeah. We're gonna blow
claymores as we move.
-Sam?
-Yes, sir?
Alpha Two, be advised,
we'll be blowing claymores.
Oh, fuck, I got a bunch
of C4 in my bag.
I gotta get my shit.
- Roger.
- Yeah, I'm gonna get it.
Sam, Tommy.
-Let's go.
-Coming. Coming.
My shit's to the left.
His gear's in the corner.
- Cover me.
- I got you.
I got Frank's shit
right here.
God.
How we doing?
Yeah, I'm up. It's cool.
- Tommy, on me.
- All right.
All right.
-I got your kit.
-Med bag. Thanks, Mac.
-That's your kit.
-We're good.
Laerrus,
give me some hands!
Yeah. Moving.
- Clip him in.
- Yes, sir.
Tommy?
OP-2, this is One.
We are breaking down,
getting ready to move. Over.
Yo, someone clip me in.
Yeah, Tommy, on me.
There is an M79
in that room there.
- Oh, shit, it's mine. Mine.
- You got it?
Sam, sledgehammer
is in front of you.
- Lock me in. Lock me in.
- I got ya.
Helmet's behind.
You got that?
Who's got that?
- Yep.
- All right.
- Hook me up.
- Yep.
Frank, you let me know
when we're up on gear.
- Sir.
- I need my backpack.
Is there any more gear
in that room, Tommy?
Uh...
Negative.
Okay.
Helmet.
Over here, brother.
Fuck.
All right.
We're all right.
-We're up!
-Copy.
Go, Mac.
Alpha Two, we're about
to blow claymores.
Blow claymores, Sam.
- Roger.
- Fire in the hole!
Go!
Last man!
I got the window.
I have the door.
This is Bushmaster.
Your cas-evac is inbound.
We are six minutes
from your position. Over.
Sir, six minutes out.
-Copy, Bushmaster.
-Okay. Go, go.
Alpha Two, we're preparing
to receive cas-evac platform.
Are you guys broken down yet?
- One, not yet.
- Check.
All right.
Here's the breakout plan.
Mac, Laerrus,
you're covering the family.
Yes, sir.
When the tank rolls up, Frank,
you're gonna pop smoke.
-Check.
-Scouts are gonna lead us out.
It's gonna be Tommy,
Elliott, Sam.
And I'm bringing up the rear.
Ray, you're with me.
Once Elliott is in the tank,
we are all coming back
inside the building.
All right. Do it.
No sudden movements.
No talking.
And keep
their hands
where these men can see them.
Frogman, this is Bushmaster.
Advise on how to receive you.
Over.
Bushmaster,
we'll be extracting two pax,
exiting out a metal gate
directly...
-Where's your smoke?
-...outside our building,
marked by HC. Over.
- Back right pocket.
- Copy, Frogman.
Two pax, metal gate.
ETA five minutes. Over.
Copy, Bushmaster.
Five minutes, sir.
All right.
Alpha Two, when the tank rolls
up, we're gonna break out.
Once we get Elliott evacuated,
we're pulling back
to our house.
Break.
-With me.
-What? Why?
-Sir, why? What is planned?
-We need to cover this door.
Anything we can do
to facilitate your movement
to us?
Just don't fucking
shoot us when we roll up.
-You cover this door.
-Why, sir?
Just do it, okay?
All right.
Hey. Mac.
-Are we good in there?
-Yeah, we're good.
- We're a few minutes out here.
- Yes, sir.
All right.
Hey, find out for me
whether the tank is gonna be
left side or right side.
Yes, sir.
Bushmaster,
this is Frogman-6 Romeo.
What side of the gate
will you be landing? Over.
- How you doing?
- I'm good.
Left hand side.
Left hand side. Over.
-Left hand side, sir.
-Copy.
Yeah, that fucking claymore
rocked me, dude.
Fucking rung my bell.
Do me a favor.
Check on Tommy.
He was pretty close
to that grenade.
Yeah.
Elliott, you good?
Good.
I'm good. I'm good.
-Okay?
-Yeah, bro.
-Yeah? Let me see it.
-Yeah, I'm good.
Fuck.
We are 10 minutes
behind. Unable to breakout.
Oh, fuck me.
Um...
Roger that.
Cache made aware
and ready to receive wounded.
Three mikes out
from your position.
Copy, Bushmaster.
-Three mikes out.
-All right.
Sir, what's going on?
-You are holding security.
-Yes.
We are gonna bust out,
go to the Bradleys.
I'm gonna get in a Bradley,
you guys are
gonna come back to the house.
Just like before.
Everything is okay.
All right?
Frogman, Frogman,
we are two mikes. Over.
Copy that.
Two mikes.
Two mikes out. Pass.
-Mac. Mac.
-Frank.
Two minutes. Two minutes.
Tommy, you okay?
You good?
Frank, I hear it.
Prep the smoke.
Smoke's prepped.
Frogman-6 Romeo,
approaching your OP now.
One minute out.
One minute.
-One minute.
Tommy?
Sir.
All right, Frank. Smoke out.
Smoke out.
Frogman,
we ID your smoke.
Thirty seconds.
Hey, stay in the stack.
Stay in the stack.
Ramps down.
Ramps down. Ramps down.
We're gonna go.
Breakout, breakout, breakout!
Go. Go.
Hold up.
Go.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Fuck!
Fuck!
Oh, my God!
No!
Ah!
Oh, my God!
Oh, God!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hey. Get air.
Sir.
Wild Eagle Base,
Wild Eagle 2-6.
When platform is available,
push to my pos.
Advise on ETA when...
This is Bushmaster.
We are troops in contact.
We've just experienced
a large IED.
We have to RTB at this time.
How copy? Over.
Bushmaster,
this is Manchu.
Solid copy on troops in
contact, what's your sit-rep?
Yeah,
upon arrival at OP-1,
er, we were ramps down
before the Frogman element
was able to...
Hang in there.
We had
a massive IED. Break.
Our gunner took some frags.
We're gonna have
to RTB this cache.
On me! One on me!
We're gonna
need assistance
off-loading our casualties.
Over.
Solid copy on all,
Bushmaster.
Proceed and de-conflict
with medical personnel
at front gate
of Camp Corregidor.
Alpha Three,
this is Alpha Two.
What's your status? Over.
Wilco. Understand.
Alpha Two, negative.
Er, we're still taking
effective fire.
Can you assist?
We're receiving
small arms fire.
We got Dash 2 in tow.
Roger. Understand.
Have you sustained
any injuries?
- Fuck.
- Hold on, Manchu.
Not at this time.
I got
Dash 2 in tow.
We're receiving a lot of
rocket and small arms fire.
Machine gun on rooftop.
Tommy, what the fuck
are you doing?
I need you to help me.
Get the fuck out here now!
Hey, can we get
some guns up here?
Frogman-6,
this is 5. Radio check.
Give me a good base
of fire up there. Stand by.
I'll be sending some guns
up to you.
Break. Alpha Three,
this is Alpha Two.
We are pushing guys
to our rooftop.
Bushmaster,
copies all.
Elliott, you're good.
Are you in contact
with the Frogman?
Is that
situation over there?
That's a negative,
Bushmaster.
A-ffirm. We're
getting the same thing here.
Understand.
Understand. Break. Break.
Alpha One, this is Alpha Two.
Radio check.
Frogman,
this is Bushmaster.
Radio check. Over.
Frogman-6, passing
in the blind to your location.
Frogman,
Bushmaster. Radio check. Over.
All elements be
prepared to break down.
Zawi, I need you to break down
in approximately one minute.
Over.
Negative on comms
with the Frogman element.
Roger that,
we are coming in now.
Will attempt continuously...
Frogman-6,
this is 5.
Advise you
attempt it on your end. Over.
What's your status?
Stand by.
Prior to breaking out,
we either gonna
blow those claymores
or we gotta swoop them up.
Fuck!
Alpha Two, this is One.
We have taken
massive casualties.
We're anticipating coordinated
enemy attack
at our position at any moment.
We need you to collapse to us.
Time, now!
Jake, this is One.
Collapse to us, now!
I'm tracking,
but where are you guys?
We're by...
We're b...
Look for the blood
and the smoke. We're there!
Two rooms deep!
What was that?
Fuck!
Two rooms deep!
No, no, don't, don't...
Fuck, fuck!
Don't touch!
Go, go, go.
Hang on. Hang on.
Jake, what's your update?
Alpha One,
this is Alpha Two.
We're experiencing effective
fire from across the street.
Um, we're looking at trying
to break out of here
once it gets soft. Stand by.
Copy that. Just fucking hurry.
Yeah, wilco.
Hey. I gotta do a blood sweep.
Fuck! Fuck!
Okay. All right. All right.
All right, Elliott.
I'm right here.
Just hang in there.
You're not alone, man.
You're okay. Rolling you over.
You're okay. You're okay.
Your back's okay.
You're good. All right?
You're good.
Come on.
All right. You're gonna
feel a little bit of pressure.
Oh, no.
I got you. Sit down.
Hey, you need to sit down.
Get the fuck down!
Stay in the room!
It's coming over your boot
right now, all right, man.
All right. Just hold on.
It's just...
Oh, man, your shoe.
It's, uh...
Oh, man,
that's not gonna work, okay.
Here's what
we're gonna do, all right.
Sir?
- Yeah?
- Apply pressure.
Like this, down.
Manchu-6 X-Ray,
this is Frogman-6 Romeo.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
This is Manchu X-Ray,
advise on number
of casualties.
Manchu-6 X-Ray,
this is Frogman-6 Romeo.
We have two severely wounded.
We need another cas-evac
as soon as possible.
Be advised an IED caused
the injuries. Over.
Here's what we need to do.
Okay, all right.
Okay.
Your leg's
like a tree trunk, man.
Frogman, you are broken
and unreadable. Say again.
Manchu-6 X-Ray,
this is Frogman-6 Romeo.
We have two severely wounded.
We need another cas-evac.
Over.
Hey, who's
the severely wounded?
-Is it me?
-No, it's not you.
...this is
Profane 5-6-5-7...
- Who is it?
- It's not you.
-Mission number 3-9-0-1...
-Then who the fuck is it?
-Two by marine F-18s.
-No. Sam.
-Who is it?
-Don't worry about it.
-Checking in as fragged.
-Who is it?
-We are postured for
-a show of force at this time.
-Hey. Hey! We got air back.
We can't do gun runs
because the bad guys
are right on top of us.
But we can coordinate
a show of force.
Do you want me to do it?
Do it.
Profane 5-6,
Wild Eagle 2-4,
we need an immediate show
of force over our position,
over our position OP-1,
from south to north.
How copy. Over.
A-ffirm,
Wild Eagle 2-4.
A show of force, south
to north, inbound 30 seconds.
Fuck.
It's bleeding through.
Guys, I need more gauze!
Yeah, yeah.
Here. Here, here, here.
Okay. Okay.
Ray!
Ray, pressure!
Oh, fuck.
-What?
-What the fuck is Frank doing?
Frank! Frank!
Lock the fucking stairwell
down. There's guys up there.
Hey, bro.
I need you to take over
comms for me. You got it?
- Got you.
- Right, yeah, okay.
Wild Eagle Base,
Wild Eagle 2-6.
Requesting relay
to Manchu X-Ray.
Uh, we're receiving
small arms fire, grenades.
And we have
two severely wounded.
We need air support. Over.
It's bleeding through
too much.
Just stop, just stop,
just stop.
Please, please. Please.
Fuck.
Sam, we gotta put a tourniquet
on you, all right?
Sir.
Yeah.
Alpha One, this is Alpha Two.
What's your sit-rep
over there?
We're treating Elliott
and Sam right now.
Be advised, possible
multiple MAMs on our rooftop.
Roger that.
We're taking effective fire
from across the street.
We're 200 meters to your East.
Move, move, move!
Stand by for an ETA
on our side.
- Roger that.
- Come on.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Fuck!
Hey,
I'm gonna do something
that's gonna hurt.
I can't put the tourniquet on.
I need to apply pressure
another way.
- All right?
- No, no, no, no, no,
don't fuck...
Don't touch me. Don't t...
Don't...
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
All right.
- I... I need morphine.
- Okay.
Uh, morphine.
- Hey.
- Give me morphine.
- Jake, where are you guys?
- Hold on.
Alpha One, this is Alpha Two.
-We've broke out of OP-2.
-Guys...
Sir?
We're now 100 meters
to your location
-to the east.
-Sir, what do we do?
Yeah, we're still
on route... Be advised...
-I don't know.
-We're about two minutes out.
We're looking
at a coordinated attack.
Give it to him.
Okay... I don't
know where the morphine is.
It's in my bag. It's in my
bag. It's in the medic bag.
What, your, in the medic bag?
It's in the pocket.
Okay, I'm getting it, I'm
getting it, I'm getting it.
Hey, Ray. I need morphine too.
You gotta give me some.
-Ray, give it to me.
-Okay.
I got it, I got it, I got it,
I got it, I got it.
Give it to me straight.
Shoot!
- Shoot.
- Sir!
Hey.
You fucked up?
I did it upside down. I did it
in my, uh, in my own thumb.
You all right though?
You good?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Bro, bro,
you there, bro?
-Yeah.
-You gotta get another one.
There's more in there!
Right.
Get another one out.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
We're still pushing to you.
Pushing to your location,
OP-1. ETA, five minutes.
We're taking effective
fire from multiple rooftops.
Okay. It's coming,
it's coming.
Hey, man.
Hey. Elliott,
it's in your arm right now,
all right?
It's in your arm.
The morphine's in
your arm, it's going into you.
You're gonna feel better
any second.
I need more morphine, man.
- You can't have more.
- It's not enough.
I'm telling you,
it's not enough.
you're good.
You're not even the one
we're worried about.
Okay?
Wild Eagle Base, Profane 5-6,
we are flying to you.
We're overhead.
We are contact.
The friendlies, the Frogmen,
moving from south to north.
And tally the individuals,
they are taking contact
from the north.
Taking contact
from the north. Uh...
Profane 5-6 is, uh,
contact several individuals.
They are using rooftops
along Frogmen's position.
They are using the rooftops
going from East to West.
Uh, we are, uh,
contact the friendlies.
They are moving
from east to west as well.
And, uh, it looks like
we are picking up
the second element of Frogmen
to the West side of that,
uh, same,
uh, same, same street.
Uh, Profane 5-7,
keep your sensors
to the North
in vicinity of OP-1.
We are contact the friendlies,
uh, linking up
on that street right now.
And, uh, Profane 5-6 is,
uh, tally several individuals
that are just to the north
of the Frogman position.
Just to the north
of the Frogman position,
we have several individuals
setting up in the prone.
Just setting up an ambush
to the Frogman position.
And we are also, uh, contact
several enemy to their east
using the rooftops in vicinity
of their position. Just to...
Profane 5-6,
this is 1-0-8.
Be advised,
we are reaching OP-1 position.
Advise on all enemy positions.
AJ! AJ!
Zawi,
I'm coming to you!
Fucking bump 'em out,
- bump 'em out!
- Ready to move!
-Three, two, one, move.
-Fucking move!
Let's fucking move!
-Changing!
- Changing!
- 0-8,
-stand by for sit-rep.
-Hold! Hold!
Move, move, move, go, go, go!
Hold!
Move! Let's move!
Driveway! Driveway! Go! Go!
Move! Go, go, go!
One, this is Two.
We're coming to you.
We have eyes on you.
On the gate!
Come on, let's move, move.
Move left to right!
Covering!
Hold this position.
They're coming to us.
- Move!
- Go!
- AJ...
- Zawi, move!
-Go, go, go, go!
-Moving!
- On me!
- Contact rooftop!
Contact rooftop!
One, this is Two.
We're coming.
We're fucking coming.
On me!
Frogman-6, Frogman-5.
Prepping smoke!
Smoke out!
- Ready?
- No.
We gotta move!
Right now, let's go. Come on.
Frogman-6, this is
Frogman-5 Romeo. Stand by.
Right, we're moving,
we're moving.
Frogman,
Frogman, coming in.
Move, Brock!
- Move, move, move!
- Ready!
Fucking move!
Last man!
Frogman,
Frogman, coming in.
All right, check it out.
We got multiple
leg injuries here.
I need morphine. Gauze.
Whatever you guys got.
We got windows in every...
Hey, watch out.
We got windows
in every inch of this house
and we got dudes on our roof.
We need to get these guys
the fuck out of here, now.
Have you called for cas-evac?
I can't punch out from here.
Go, get up there.
Zawi, go.
-Can you make comms?
-Yes, sir.
Sir.
Has anyone looked at you,
checked you out?
Hey, take a knee,
take a knee, take a knee.
Take a knee.
Has anyone looked at you?
Let me do a blood-sweep.
Manchu X-Ray,
this is Frogman-5 Romeo.
Be advised,
OP-2 have consolidated
on OP-1 position.
How copy. Over.
Is the cas-evac platform
coming back here?
-What calls have been made?
-Dude...
I'm fucked up.
I'm gonna need you
to run point.
-What's going on up there?
-All right,
we got grenades thrown
in this room over here.
We've probably got, probably
got dudes on our roof still.
All right.
This is the external door,
straight ahead, all right?
-Yeah.
-On me.
Gonna need some ammo, dude.
All right, I'll get it to you.
Let's go.
Go.
Hit in both of his legs
and hit in his arm.
And he's got abdomen wounds,
and, man,
he's lost a lot of blood.
-Okay.
-And, uh,
there's something burning
inside of him.
Yeah,
that's phosphorous.
It's all over outside.
Elliott, can you breathe?
Hmm.
- Yeah. All right.
- You're good. You're good.
You guys hit me
with that fucking morphine?
Yeah, I gave you the morphine.
I gave you the morphine, man.
- When?
- A few minutes ago.
Right before you got here.
Did you do it
in my arm?
'Cause I got shitty blood
return in my legs.
I did it in your arm, man.
I did it right in your arm.
Move, move, move!
Move, move! Move!
Let's go, boys!
Let's fucking do this!
Hey! Hey!
I know we're moving fast,
but don't step
on anyone's fucking legs!
All right, Sammy. Let's go.
Relax, man.
My man, let's do this!
Come on!
Don't fuck with him!
Stay in there, Sam,
stay in there.
All right, guys, listen up.
Everybody shut the fuck up.
Eyes on me.
Start doing a re-org.
Prepare for breakout.
We're gonna get
these guys cas-evacced.
Yes, sir.
- All right.
- Yo, Brock.
Yo, what's up, Frank?
You got ammo
for the gunners upstairs?
Yeah, outside pocket.
I want four Bradleys
over here.
Two for cas-evac,
two for extraction.
I want the cas-evacs on
either side of the front gate.
Brad one will be right.
Brad two left.
Yes, sir.
Hey, lock down the windows!
Thank you.
Go.
Fuck!
We can't make it.
This is Frogman-5 Romeo.
We need a cas-evac
from OP-1 building.
Four Bradleys.
Two for cas-evac of two
severely wounded. Break.
Hell, man, get off me!
Stay in there, bro.
You're good.
Relax. Hey.
He's fucking good, man.
-It's a fucking paper cut!
-Hey.
You're a fucking Frogman, Sam!
-He doesn't need this!
-He's a fucking Frogman!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Fuck!
Fucking A.
Frogman,
Manchu, you are denied
Bradley cas-evac due to IED,
small arms threat in the AO.
-Authorization pending...
-Fuck.
...CO approval.
How copy. Over.
Solid copy. Stand by.
Sir.
They're waiting
on Brigade approval.
What the fuck?
Because the last tanks
got fucked up.
So they won't send a cas-evac
unless the CO
gives the thumbs up.
We gotta get him
out of here, sir.
You've gotta be the CO.
Sir. Say back.
Radio them right now.
Say you're the CO.
Give them the order
to send the fucking Brads.
Roger that.
Hey, Tommy, lock it down.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
What happened?
- I don't know.
- Was it an IED, what?
I don't fucking know, bro.
I just wanna get
the fuck out of here.
Yeah.
Manchu X-Ray,
this is Manchu-6.
I authorize Bushmaster.
How copy. Over.
A-ffirm,
Manchu-6. Break.
Frogman-5 Romeo, be ready to
receive Bushmaster on 7-5-5.
How copy. Over.
Wilco. Bushmaster 7-5-5.
Bushmaster is approved
to maneuver to our position.
Mikey, Brian, give me
an update on the roof.
Taking effective enemy fire!
Multiple bad guys
on the rooftops!
Bushmaster is approved.
I'll give you a shout.
You okay?
-Let me know. You good?
-Yeah, I'm good.
Is there
a rug in there?
You're good, man.
I'm right here.
- You're good.
- On it.
Are we all up on gear?
AJ,
any gear out there?
There's gear in the street.
John, with me.
Fuck!
Collapse, collapse.
Collapse, collapse, collapse!
- Collapse!
- Fuck!
Zawi!
Bradleys are four minutes out!
You got four mikes.
They're
pushing in on us!
We gotta get off
this fucking rooftop!
Zawi!
Get back! Get back!
Zawi.
Zawi!
Motherfucker!
What's going on? Cas-evac
inbound. I need a 5W.
Had to suck back.
Unable to hold position.
We got multiple bad guys
trying to get to our position.
Sir. Sir, I'm calling in
a show of force.
Profane 5-6-5-7,
Wild Eagle 2-6,
-requesting an immediate...
-When the Bradleys get here,
-Mac, Aaron, Tommy...
-...show of force over
-OP-1's position.
-...you grab Elliott.
You guys are gonna
go out first.
You're going to go into
Brad one. Right hand side.
- Right hand side. Check.
- Yes, sir.
Ray, Brock, grab Sam.
-Brad two. Left side.
-Got it.
- Three minutes out!
- Three minutes!
Wild Eagle Base,
tracking Bushmaster now.
They are en route
to you now, OP-1.
- Hey, hey.
- Yeah.
I got his legs.
You got his arms?
-Yeah, let's get him ready.
-All right.
-Let's get this shit sorted.
-Gonna get you out of here.
Get that rug.
All right, we're gonna
get you the fuck out of here.
- I got him, I got him.
- Come on,
give me your hand, brother.
All right.
- Watch his arm, watch his arm!
- We're gonna get
- the fuck out of here, okay?
- All right.
Right here. Right here.
Okay, okay.
Right, now let's fold him,
okay?
Tommy, on you.
We're gonna fold him your way.
- On my count.
- Guys,
if you're gonna move me,
you gotta move me real fast.
- Yeah, we will. All right.
- All right.
- Whoa!
- On my count.
- All right.
All right, on three.
One, two, three!
All right.
Come on, come on!
One, two, three!
- We good?
- Set him down.
All right, you're good,
you're good, right?
Other side, other side,
we got this.
- All right, Aaron.
- One, two, three.
All right,
all right. Okay.
- Two minutes out!
- Two minutes!
All right,
and at three, two, one.
you're doing great.
- You hear that?
- Don't forget my fucking arm!
Don't worry, bro,
your arm's still attached.
It's right here. I got it.
- Two minutes out!
- Two minutes!
Wild Eagle Base, Profane.
Bushmaster appears to be
approximately 100 meters out
at this time.
Hey, you gotta get ready, man.
This is gonna hurt.
No, no, no, there's gotta be
another way, man.
-There's gotta be another way.
-There's no other way, man.
-No, don't fucking touch me.
-We gotta do it.
-Don't fucking touch...
-BTF-up, bro!
What side
are we getting Elliott out?
Elliott...
Inbound!
Elliott right side,
Sam on the left side.
Elliott right. Roger that.
- One minute out!
- One minute!
Tommy, I got Elliott.
Tommy, Frank,
you two are breaking us out.
-Check.
-Yes, sir.
Gunners, you'll set up
security out on the street.
Frank, you straight?
I'm good.
I'm gonna buttonhook right.
Copy that.
I'm taking the right Bradley.
Frogman,
this is Bushmaster.
We are approaching OP-1
at this time.
Frank, Tommy.
-We good?
-Good to go.
When we break out
of here, eyes on me
- and only me, all right?
- Ray, Brock,
-you good?
-We're good!
Bradleys are here!
All right.
Let's get him on three.
- Three, two, one.
- Two, one.
Ramp down, ramp down,
ramp down, ramp down.
- Breakout, breakout, breakout!
- Go!
- Watch his legs.
- Let's go!
I'm stuck.
Right, Brock, let's move.
One, two, three, up!
Move!
- Move!
- Right side! Right side!
Move! Move!
All right. One! Two! Three!
- I'm out!
- Come on, brother, we got you!
Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Move, move! Come on.
Changing!
Go, go, go, go, go!
AJ, 1 o'clock!
Fucking good!
- Three o'clock!
- Ramp up!
- Collapse!
- Ramp up! Ramp up!
Mac! Mac!
We have to collapse.
-Let's go.
-Wait, wait!
To the house.
You all right?
- You all right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
I just...
Thought you were hit.
I just tripped.
Let's go, let's go!
Last man! Last man!
Hey, come on, man, giddy-up.
I didn't make it out.
I'm stuck in the Bradley.
Over.
Redman 0-8,
this is Profane.
We're seeing
activity converging
on the rooftops
on all sides of OP-1.
We need you to de-conflict
any friendlies.
Profane says the guys
are moving to our roof.
They're telling us to get our
guys off the roof right now.
Do we still have guys
up there?
- We're the last guys up there.
- They're right on us.
Zawi, you hold security
and lock it down.
Check.
Listen up! I'm gonna
have the Bradleys
take out the second floor
of this building!
Gunners, you're holding
security out on the street
- for extract.
- Yes, sir!
Mac, I want a show of force
for when that happens.
- Yes, sir. Sergeant.
- Yeah.
Bushmaster 1-1.
Need you to fire into
top deck of our building.
We have enemy on our building
and all surrounding buildings.
Say again.
Fire into your building?
We got a full head count.
Fire into our building.
Top deck.
Zawi, get the fuck down here!
Negative, Frogman.
We can't do that.
The top deck is fucking clear.
Fire into it.
Roger that. Stand by.
-Going hot.
- Suck in!
- Find cover!
- Let's go!
Get down! Get down! Get down!
We're breaking out hot!
- Gunners up!
- Let's move!
Gunners up!
Frogman, Bushmaster.
Shifting fire, going hot.
Why?
- Why? Why?
- I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-Why?
Inbound! Inbound!
Stand by!
Breakout, breakout!
One! Two!
Three!
-Last man!
-Moving!
Let's go!
We're out!
Get the fucking ramp up!
You made it. I didn't
think you were gonna make it.
I had a bet.
I lost the fucking bet.